[{"question":"\tMary’s","option":"","answer":" score on the test is the highest in her class; she ________ have studied very hard.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\t________","option":"","answer":" that the trade between the two countries reached its highest point.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tHe","option":"","answer":" suggested ________ to tomorrow’s exhibition together.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tNo","option":"","answer":" agreement was reached in the discussion as neither side would give way to ________.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tWith","option":"","answer":" agreement was reached I the discussion as neither side would give way to ________.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tIf","option":"","answer":" you want ________ you have to get the fund somewhere.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tThere","option":"","answer":" is more land in Australia than the government knows ________.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tIt’s","option":"","answer":" no use ________ me not to worry.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tI","option":"","answer":" have two boys but ________ of them likes sweets.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tOnly","option":"","answer":" by shouting at the top of his voice ________.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\t________","option":"","answer":" such a good chance, he planned to learn more.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tIf","option":"","answer":" it ________ too much trouble, I’d love a cup of tea.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tMy","option":"","answer":" sister’s professor had her ________ her paper many times before allowing her to present it to the committee.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tsilver","option":"","answer":" is the best conductor of electricity, copper ________ it closely.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tThey","option":"","answer":" are considering ________ before the prices go up.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tShe","option":"","answer":" was glad that her success would ________ for the women who would follow.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tThey","option":"","answer":" will have it finished in ________.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tA","option":"","answer":" Dream of the Red Chamber is said ________ into dozens of languages in the last decade.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tHe","option":"","answer":" went ahead ________ all warnings about the danger of his mission.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tWe","option":"","answer":" object ________ punishing a whole group for one person’s fault.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tJack","option":"","answer":" is good, kind, hard-working and intelligent; ________; I can’t speak too highly of him.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tThe","option":"","answer":" man to whom we handed the forms pointed out that they had not been ________ filled in.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tI","option":"","answer":" shall have companion in the house after all these ________ years.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tAfter","option":"","answer":" a long and exhausting journey, they arrived ________.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tNone","option":"","answer":" of the servants were ________ when Mr. Smith wanted to send a message.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tI","option":"","answer":" can’t ________ what that object is.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tI","option":"","answer":" want to buy a new tie to ________ this brown suit.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tThe","option":"","answer":" newest satellite can ________ a thousand telephone conversations and a colour TV program at the same time.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tI","option":"","answer":" can ________ some noise while I’m studying, but I can’t stand loud noises.","difficulty":2},{"question":"\tWhen","option":"","answer":" the whole area was ________ by the flood, the government sent food there by helicopter.","difficulty":2}]